<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-02-06T01:26:48-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">@fullarray</title><subtitle>I'm a naturally curious software, IT, and systems engineer. I enjoy finding technology-based solutions. In my free time, I like to go to the beach and cruise by A1A on the Florida coastline.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Programming is awesome if it’s practiced frequently</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/programming/2017/11/12/programming-is-awesome.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Programming is awesome if it's practiced frequently" /><published>2017-11-12T00:40:13-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-12T00:40:13-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/programming/2017/11/12/programming-is-awesome</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/programming/2017/11/12/programming-is-awesome.html">&lt;p&gt;This is just a thought that has floated around in many companies internal development teams. The idea that talented developers are significantly scarce is a reality. But why?. This bold assertion lays in the fact that many to-be developers don’t practice as much as their senior counterparts. Another possible reason is that to-be developers are impatient and would like to get up and running in virtually no time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact that programming is an art is ignored by many, but if a person is to become a developer several hours, days, weeks, and years are needed to reach a comfortable level necessary to perform at a junior and senior developer level.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">This is just a thought that has floated around in many companies internal development teams. The idea that talented developers are significantly scarce is a reality. But why?. This bold assertion lays in the fact that many to-be developers don’t practice as much as their senior counterparts. Another possible reason is that to-be developers are impatient and would like to get up and running in virtually no time.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What is the Spring Web Framework</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/java/2017/11/10/what-is-the-spring-web-framework.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What is the Spring Web Framework" /><published>2017-11-10T00:40:13-05:00</published><updated>2017-11-10T00:40:13-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/java/2017/11/10/what-is-the-spring-web-framework</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/java/2017/11/10/what-is-the-spring-web-framework.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll probably noticed the increased amount of web traffic. It’s inevitable. We as society have increasily incorporated the internet into our lifestyles. This has cause companies to innovate and come up with new solutions that keep their customers interested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is where the Spring framework makes its appearance. The Spring framework is a Java-based library that caters to web developers and engineers. It seeks to fill the gap that Java J2EE cannot. Even though J2EE plays a major role in the Java web development ecosystem for many Java Full stack developers, the Spring Framework takes a different approach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main idea from the Spring framework is to reduce the time it takes to develop applications. It does this by providing pre-fabricated software tools, functions, and objects. This in return improve development significantly allowing applications to be deployed within minutes, ready for testing and debugging. The Spring Framework is ideal for development teams that rely heavily on prototyping.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’ll probably noticed the increased amount of web traffic. It’s inevitable. We as society have increasily incorporated the internet into our lifestyles. This has cause companies to innovate and come up with new solutions that keep their customers interested.</summary></entry></feed>